Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive, 1966-2000 (bulk 1970-1995) MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Video Recordings, 145934
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals, 145935
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice--Film Background, ID: 133.0106; 162219 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0106)
    - Prelude to Death in Venice Sample Video Version, 1986; ID: 133.0107; 162220 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0107)
    - Prelude Film Sample, 1986; ID: 133.0108; 162221 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0108)
    - The Lost Ones, 1976; ID: 133.0109; 162226 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0109)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0731
    - The Lost Ones, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0110; 162225 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0110)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0734
    - The Lost Ones, 1976; ID: 133.0111; 162222 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0111)
    - WNET/Thirteen Gosepl at Colonus Part 1., 1986; ID: 133.0114; 162228 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0114)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID # 133.0737
    - Gospel at Colonus Part II, 1986; ID: 133.0115; 162227 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0115)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0740
    - Copy of Breuer Red Horse Rehearsal, 1995; ID: 133.0119; 162223 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0119)
    - Red Horse Rehearsal, 1995; ID: 133.0120; 162224 (Box 146, Media ID: 133.0120)
    - King Lear-Olivier Version, 1984; ID: 133.0124; 162245 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0124)
    - King Lear - Olivier Version, 1984; ID: 133.0125; 162246 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0125)
    - King Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0126; 162247 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0126)
    - Selections from the Mabou Mines/Lee Breuer "Lear" Workshop, 1987; ID: 133.0127; 162231 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0127)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0743
    - Mabou Mines' Lear [Selected Scenes], 1987; ID: 133.0128; 162248 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0128)
    - Jill Godmilow's Lear Tapes, 1987; ID: 133.0129; 162249 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0129)
    - Jill Godmilow's The Lear Tapes [Work in Progress], 1987; ID: 133.0130; 162250 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0130)
    - Cuts from Lear, 1988; ID: 133.0131; 162251 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0131)
    - Mabou Mines' LEAR [1 of 3], 1988; ID: 133.0132; 162236 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0132)
    - Mabou Mines' LEAR [2 of 3], 1988; ID: 133.0133; 162237 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0133)
    - Mabou Mines' LEAR [3 of 3], 1988; ID: 133.0134; 162238 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0134)
    - Mabou Mines' LEAR [Master] Work in Progress., 1988; ID: 133.0135; 162233 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0135)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0746
    - Lear Work-in-Progress, 1988; ID: 133.0136; 162239 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0136)
    - Lear 2., 1988; ID: 133.0137; 162232 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0137)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0749
    - Lear 4., 1988; ID: 133.0138; 162235 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0138)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0752
    - Lear 3., 1988; ID: 133.0139; 162234 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0139)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0755
    - Lear at Smith, 1989; ID: 133.0140; 162240 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0140)
    - Jill Godmilow's tape of LEAR at Smith College, 1989; ID: 133.0141; 162241 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0141)
    - Lear at Smith College, 1989; ID: 133.0142; 162242 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0142)
    - Jill Godmilow's tape of LEAR at Smith College, 1989; ID: 133.0143; 162243 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0143)
    - Lear at Smith College, 1989; ID: 133.0146; 162244 (Box 147, Media ID: 133.0146)
    - Lear at Smith College, 1989; ID: 133.0147; 162255 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0147)
    - Lear at Smith College, [1989]; ID: 133.0148; 162256 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0148)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [1990]; ID: 133.0149; 162257 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0149)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, 1990; ID: 133.0150; 162258 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0150)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [1990]; ID: 133.0151; 162259 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0151)
    - Lear Performance, 1990; ID: 133.0156; 162260 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0156)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0758
    - Lear Performance, 1990; ID: 133.0157; 162261 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0157)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0761
    - Lear Performance, 1990; ID: 133.0158; 162262 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0158)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0764
    - Lear at Triplex, [1990]; ID: 133.0159; 162265 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0159)
    - Lear at Triplex, 1990; ID: 133.0160; 162264 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0160)
    - Lear at Triplex, 1990; ID: 133.0161; 162263 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0161)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, 1991; ID: 133.0162; 162266 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0162)
    - Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0163; 162267 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0163)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0164; 162268 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0164)
    - 10 Cuts from Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0165; 162269 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0165)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0166; 162270 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0166)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0167; 162271 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0167)
    - King Lear, [1975]; ID: 133.0168; 162272 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0168)
    - King Lear, [1975]; ID: 133.0169; 162273 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0169)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0173; 162278 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0173)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0174; 162277 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0174)
    - King Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0175; 162276 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0175)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0176; 162274 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0176)
    - Mabou Mines' Lear, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0177; 162275 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0177)
    - Jill Godmilow's Lear Tape, 1999; ID: 133.0178A; 162279 (Box 148, Media ID: 133.0178A)
    - Lee Breuer's Hajj (in performance), 1987; ID: 133.0179; 162281 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0179)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0767
    - Lee Breuer's Hajj (in performance), 1987; ID: 133.0180; 162282 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0180)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0770
    - Hajj Out Take #1A, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0181; 162283 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0181)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0773
    - Hajj Out Take #1B, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0182; 162284 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0182)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0776
    - Hajj Out Take #2, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0183; 162285 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0183)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0779
    - Hajj Out Take #3A, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0184; 162286 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0184)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0782
    - Hajj Out Take #3B, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0185; 162287 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0185)
      3/4 in Umatic
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0785
    - Hajj Out Take #4A, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0186; 162288 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0186)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0788
    - Hajj Out Take #4B, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0187; 162280 (Box 149, Media ID: 133.0187)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0791
    - Hajj Out Take #4C, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0188; 162289 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0188)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0794
    - Lies, 1981; ID: 133.0189; 162290 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0189)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0797
    - Hajj (Lies) #3A, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0190; 272005 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0190)
    - Hajj Center Pt. 1, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0191; 272001 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0191)
    - Hajj NBC Master Tape, 1983; ID: 133.0192A; 162292 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0192A)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0800
    - Hajj, 1985; ID: 133.0193; 162291 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0193)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0803
    - Hajj [Dissolve Center] Copy I, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0194; 162293 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0194)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0806
    - Hajj Master II Dissolve, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0195; 162294 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0195)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0809
    - AFI Video Festival: Dub of News Report., 1982; ID: 133.0196; 162295 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0196)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0812
    - AFI Video Festival: Hajj I, 1982; ID: 133.0197; 162296 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0197)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0815
    - Mabou Mines' "Hajj", [n.d.]; ID: 133.0198; 162297 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0198)
    - Hajj Work Sample, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0199; 162298 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0199)
    - Hajj DTW, 1986; ID: 133.0200; 162299 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0200)
    - Hajj Center Pt.I, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0201; 162300 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0201)
      S-VHS
    - Hajj Center Pt. I, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0202; 162301 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0202)
    - Hajj Dissolve Right Side, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0203; 162302 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0203)
    - Mabou Mines' Hajj Left Monitor, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0204; 162303 (Box 150, Media ID: 133.0204)
    - Dead End Kids 2nd Take, 1982; ID: 133.0207; 162329 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0207)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0821
    - Dead End Kids Act II, [1982]; ID: 133.0208; 162330 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0208)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0824
    - Dead End Kids [Film Version], 1982; ID: 133.0210; 162331 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0210)
    - Dead End Kids Workprint [Film Version - New Improved Color], 1982; ID: 133.0211; 162323 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0211)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0827
    - Dead End Kids Workprint [Film Version], [1982]; ID: 133.0212; 162332 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0212)
    - Dead End Kids Workprint [Film Version], 1982; ID: 133.0213; 162322 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0213)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0830
    - Dead End Kids Workprint [Film Version], 1982; ID: 133.0214A; 162333 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0214A)
    - Dead End Kids Film Workprint [Film Version], ID: 133.0215; 162324 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0215)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0833
    - Dead End Kids / Franklin & Jefferson., 1983; ID: 133.0216; 162325 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0216)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0836
    - Dead End Kids, 1985; ID: 133.0217; 162328 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0217)
    - Dead End Kids: A History of Nuclear Power [Film Version], ID: 133.0218; 162326 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0218)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0839DVD access copy available. Please request ID #
    - Dead End Kids: A History of Nuclear Power [Film Version] Part II, ID: 133.0219; 162327 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0219)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0842
    - Dead End Kids: A History of Nuclear Power [Film Version], 1985; ID: 133.0220; 162334 (Box 151, Media ID: 133.0220)
    - Dead End Kids: A History of Nuclear Power [Film Version], 1985; ID: 133.0221; 162343 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0221)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], ID: 133.0222; 162342 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0222)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power, ID: 133.0223; 162341 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0223)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], ID: 133.0224; 162340 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0224)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], ID: 133.0225; 162339 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0225)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], 1983; ID: 133.0226; 162337 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0226)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], 1983; ID: 133.0227; 162336 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0227)
    - Dead End Kids Clips [Film Version], 1982; ID: 133.0228; 162335 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0228)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], 1989; ID: 133.0229; 162349 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0229)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], 1989; ID: 133.0230; 162348 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0230)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], 1989; ID: 133.0231; 162347 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0231)
    - Dead End Kids: A Story of Nuclear Power [Film Version], ID: 133.0232; 162338 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0232)
    - 0152 Mabou Mines Development Foundation, ID: 133.0233; 162345 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0233)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0845
    - Mabou Mines [Imagination Dead Imagine - Interviews: Raw Footage], 1986; ID: 133.0234; 162344 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0234)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0848
    - Dead End Kids Film [Film Version], ID: 133.0235; 162346 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0235)
    - Joanne Akalartis, November 8, 1990; ID: 133.0237; 272002 (Box 152, Media ID: 133.0237)
    - Imagination Dead-Imagine Excerpts, 1984; ID: 133.0238; 162357 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0238)
    - Imagination Dead-Imagine Excerpts, 1984; ID: 133.0239; 162358 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0239)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine [Master], 1984; ID: 133.0240A; 162354 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0240A)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0851
    - Boston Music Viva: New Works., 1984; ID: 133.0242A; 162353 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0242A)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0854
    - Imagination, 1986; ID: 133.0243; 162356 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0243)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0857
    - Imagination Dead-Imagine Excerpts, 1984; ID: 133.0244; 162355 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0244)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0860
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, 1984; ID: 133.0245; 162365 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0245)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0863
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Record Video, ID: 133.0246; 162364 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0246)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0866
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, ID: 133.0247; 162350 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0247)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Sample Tape, ID: 133.0248; 162351 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0248)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, ID: 133.0249; 162352 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0249)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, 1984; ID: 133.0251A; 162363 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0251A)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0869
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, 1984; ID: 133.0252; 162362 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0252)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0872
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, ID: 133.0253; 272003 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0253)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine, 1986; ID: 133.0254; 162361 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0254)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0875
    - Imagination Dead-Imagine Excerpts, 1984; ID: 133.0255; 162360 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0255)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0878
    - Imagination Dead Imagine: 6 1/2 minute excerpt from performance, ID: 133.0257; 162359 (Box 153, Media ID: 133.0257)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0881
    - Through the Leaves, 1990; ID: 133.0258; 162377 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0258)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0884
    - Through the Leaves, 1990; ID: 133.0261A; 162366 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0261A)
    - Idle Tears "Every Day", 1985; ID: 133.0262A; 162376 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0262A)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0887
    - It's A Man's World, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0263; 162375 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0263)
    - It's A Man's World, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0264; 162374 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0264)
    - It's A Man's World, 1985; ID: 133.0267; 162378 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0267)
    - It's A Man's World, 1985; ID: 133.0268; 162379 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0268)
    - It's A Man's World, [1985]; ID: 133.0269; 162380 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0269)
    - It's a Man's World, 1985; ID: 133.0270; 162381 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0270)
    - Mabou Mines' Reel-to-Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0271A; 162368 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0271A)
    - Reel to Real, 1994; ID: 133.0272; 162370 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0272)
    - Mabou Mines' Reel to Real, 1994; ID: 133.0273; 162369 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0273)
    - Reel to Real, 1994; ID: 133.0274; 162386 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0274)
    - Reel to Real (Early Version), [n.d.]; ID: 133.0276; 162372 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0276)
    - Reel to Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0277; 162373 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0277)
    - Reel to Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0278; 162382 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0278)
    - Reel to Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0279; 162383 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0279)
    - Reel to Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0280; 162384 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0280)
    - Reel to Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0281; 162385 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0281)
    - Reel to Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0282; 162371 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0282)
    - Reel to Real, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0283; 162367 (Box 154, Media ID: 133.0283)
    - Saint and Football Players, 1983; ID: 133.0284; 162471 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0284)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0890
    - Saint and the Football Players, 1983; ID: 133.0285; 162472 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0285)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0893
    - The Saint and the Football Players [on German TV], 1979; ID: 133.0286; 162473 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0286)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0896
    - The Saint and the Football Players, 1979; ID: 133.0287; 162474 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0287)
    - The Saint, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0289; 162475 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0289)
    - Excerpts/Raw Footage from The Saint, 1983; ID: 133.0290; 162476 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0290)
    - The Saint and the Football Players, 1973; 1983; 1979; ID: 133.0292; 162477 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0292)
    - Motherlode Workshop, 1993; ID: 133.0293A; 162478 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0293A)
    - Yellowsprings 02, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0294A; 162479 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0294A)
    - Yellow Springs Institute, 1993; ID: 133.0295; 162480 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0295)
    - 15 minute excerpt from Mabou Mines' Mother, 1994; ID: 133.0296; 162481 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0296)
    - Mother in performance at La MaMa, 1994; ID: 133.0298; 162482 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0298)
    - Inside the Piece "Mother", [n.d.]; ID: 133.0299; 162483 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0299)
    - Inside of the Piece Mother, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0301; 162484 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0301)
    - Inside of the Piece Mother, 1993; ID: 133.0302; 162485 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0302)
    - Inside of Mother, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0303; 162486 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0303)
    - Mother, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0305; 162487 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0305)
    - Mother Interviews, 1994; ID: 133.0306; 162488 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0306)
    - A Job Well Done, 1994; ID: 133.0307; 162489 (Box 155, Media ID: 133.0307)
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0308; 162511 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0308)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0899
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0309; 162490 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0309)
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0310; 162491 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0310)
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0311; 162492 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0311)
    - Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's The Warrior Ant, 1986; ID: 133.0312; 162493 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0312)
    - The Warrior Ant-The Ant in Hell, 1988; ID: 133.0314; 162494 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0314)
    - Warrior Ant @ BAM, 1988; ID: 133.0315A; 162495 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0315A)
    - Warrior Ant Raw Footage, 1988; ID: 133.0316; 162496 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0316)
    - The Warrior Ant Acts II & III, 1988; ID: 133.0317; 162497 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0317)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0319; 162498 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0319)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0320; 162499 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0320)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0321; 162500 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0321)
    - Warrior Ant, 1988; ID: 133.0322; 162501 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0322)
    - The Warrior Ant, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0323; 162502 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0323)
    - The Warrior Ant Part III, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0324; 162503 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0324)
    - The Warrior Ant, Part 4 (The Ant in Hell), 1987; ID: 133.0326; 162504 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0326)
    - Warrior Ant support materials, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0327; 162505 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0327)
    - Worstward Ho, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0328; 162506 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0328)
    - Worstward Ho in Geneva, 1991; ID: 133.0329; 162507 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0329)
    - Worstward Ho!, 1995; ID: 133.0330; 162508 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0330)
      Video 8 mm
    - Worstward Ho, 1995; ID: 133.0331; 162509 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0331)
    - Worstward Ho, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0332; 162510 (Box 156, Media ID: 133.0332)
    - Sister Suzie, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0333; 162518 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0333)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0902
    - Sister Suzie Cinema, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0334; 162521 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0334)
    - Jungle, 1st Hour, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0335; 162517 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0335)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0905
    - Jungle, 2nd Hour, ID: 133.0336; 162519 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0336)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0908
    - In the Jungle of the Cities @ The Public Theater, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0337; 162522 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0337)
    - Jungle Clip Reel, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0338; 162520 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0338)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0911
    - MahabharANTa (Mabou Minds) @ ASUW, ID: 133.0339; 162523 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0339)
    - The MahabharANTa @ Ontological Theater; @ Arts @ St. Ann's, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0340; 162524 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0340)
    - Company, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0342; 162525 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0342)
    - Tears Worktape, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0343; 162526 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0343)
    - Flow My Tears The Policeman Said, Boston, copy 1, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0344; 162527 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0344)
    - Flow My Tears, Show Tape 1 Master, 1988; ID: 133.0345; 162512 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0345)
    - Flow My Tears, Show Tape 2 Master, 1988; ID: 133.0346; 162513 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0346)
    - Flow My Tears, Doc. of Show 1, 1988; ID: 133.0347; 162514 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0347)
    - Flow My Tears, Doc. of Show 3 [Note: believed to be pt.2], 1988; ID: 133.0348; 162515 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0348)
    - Flow My Tears, Doc. of Show 2, 1988; ID: 133.0349; 162516 (Box 157, Media ID: 133.0349)
    - The 1st 20 Years, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0350; 272004 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0350)
    - The First 20 Years (rough edit), [n.d.]; ID: 133.0351; 162540 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0351)
    - The First 20 Years (not for broadcast), [n.d.]; ID: 133.0352; 162539 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0352)
    - The First 20 Years, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0353; 162538 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0353)
    - Tokuma & ITVS (Sample Reel), [n.d.]; ID: 133.0354; 162529 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0354)
      DVD access copy available. Please request ID #133.0914
    - Cuts from Lear, In the Jungle of Cities, and Through the Leaves, ID: 133.0355; 162537 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0355)
    - Cuts from Company, Worstward Ho, The First 20 Years, and Through the Leaves, ID: 133.0356; 162536 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0356)
    - Clips from Hajj and Lear, ID: 133.0357; 162535 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0357)
    - Hajj, Worstward Ho, Company, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0358; 162534 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0358)
    - It's A Man's World, Cold Harbor, [n.d.]; ID: 133.0359; 162533 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0359)
    - Saint and Football, Interviews Backstage, B-Beaver Animation, Children's Workshop, ID: 133.0360; 162532 (Box 158, Media ID: 133.0360)